data = [
    {
        "question": "JSON stands for _______.",
       "answers": {
            "a": "JavaScript Object Notation",
            "b": "Java Object Notation",
            "c": "JavaScript Object Normalization",
            "d": "JavaScript Object-Oriented Notation"},
        "correctAnswer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "JSON is a _____ for storing and transporting data.",
        "answers": {
            "a": "xml format",
            "b": "text format",
            "c": "JavaScript",
            "d": "php format"},
        "correctAnswer": "b"
    },
    {
        question: "The JSON syntax is a subset of the _____ syntax.",
        answers: {
            a: "Ajax",
            b: "php",
            c: "HTML",
            d: "JavaScript"},
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the creator of JSON",
        answers: {
            a: "Alvin Alexander",
            b: "Rasmus Lerdorf",
            c: "Douglas Crockford",
            d: "Jesse James Garrett"},
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "In the JSON syntax, data is separated by _____.",
        answers: {
            a: "Semicolons",
            b: "Colons",
            c: "Commas",
            d: "Hyper"},
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "In the JSON syntax, array is written within in ____.",
        answers: {
            a: "Square brackets",
            b: "Curley braces",
            c: "Paratheses",
            d: "None of the above"},
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the file type for JSON files?",
        answers: {
            a: ".jsn",
            b: ".js",
            c: ".json",
            d: ".jso"},
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Which is not a JSON data type?",
        answers: {
            a: "number",
            b: "string",
            c: "array",
            d: "date"},
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "A common use of JSON is ________.",
        answers: {
            a: "to update data into the database",
            b: "to retrieve data from the database",
            c: "to exchange data to/from a web server",
            d: "None of the above"},
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Which function is used to convert text into a JavaScript object?",
        answers: {
            a: "JSON.parse()",
            b: "string.parse()",
            c: "object.parse()",
            d: "All of the above"},
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Which function is used to convert a JavaScript object into a string?",
        answers: {
            a: "JSON.string()",
            b: "JSON.stringify()",
            c: "JSON.ToString()",
            d: "All of the above"},
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "______ is a method for sending JSON data without worrying about cross-domain issues.",
        answers: {
            a: "JSON",
            b: "json",
            c: "JSONP",
            d: "JSONP_Encode()"},
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "JSONP stands for _____.",
        answers: {
            a: "JSON with Packing",
            b: "JSON with Padding",
            c: "JSON with Parsing",
            d: "JSON with Prefix"},
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "What is/are the parameter(s) of the method JSON.parse()?",
        answers: {
            a: "Text",
            b: "Reviver",
            c: "Object",
            d: "Both Text and Reviver"},
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "JSON array elements can be access by ___.",
        answers: {
            a: "Name",
            b: "Key",
            c: "Value",
            d: "Index"},
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which number types are available in the JavaScript but not supported in the JSON?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Fractional and Rational",
            "b": "Infinity and Rational",
            "c": "Rational and Irrational",
            "d": "Infinity and NaN"},
        "correctAnswer": "d"
    }
]